AFL-CIO Executive Council Minutes 5881
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AFL-CIO Executive Council Minutes
1973-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO)
5881
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Minutes (administrative records).
5725216
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4158: John P. Windmuller Additional Papers /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files 5204 mf: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Records on Microfilm 5541: Philip Taft Papers 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5619: ACWA Records 5619/002: ACWA Education Department Records 5619/006: ACTWU Executive Vice-President's Office Files 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files 5619/018: ACTWU Secretary-Treasurer's Office Files 5619/033: ACTWU Legislative and Political Department Files 5619/036: ACTWU President's Office Murray Finley Files 5685: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5743 P: ACWA Photographs 5780 MB: ILGWU Memorabilia 5780 P: ILGWU Photographs 5780/062 PUBS: ILGWU International Relations Department publications 5780/083: ILGWU Sol Chaikin Papers 5780/084: ILGWU Wilbur Daniels Papers 5780/088: ILGWU Gus Tyler Papers 5780/097: ILGWU Susan Cowell Papers 5780/138: ILGWU Education Department, Kitty Krupat Papers 5780/142: ILGWU Political/Legislative Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers 5780/150: ILGWU Carl Proper Papers 5780/187: ILGWU Irwin Solomon Papers 5780/196: ILGWU Operations Department Industrial Homework Records 5780/203: ILGWU Jay Mazur Papers 5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
AFL-CIO.; AFL-CIO. Executive Council; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union.
5725216
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 32., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Large Bound Book.
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 25., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Large bound book.
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 21., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Bound book.
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 20., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 22., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 23., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 24., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes of the 1981 AFL-CIO General Board Meeting. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Chicago, Illinois. August 6 1981.
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meeting. Volume 31., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 30., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meeting. Volume 29., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 28., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 26., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Broken bound book.
- Executive Council AFL-CIO. Minutes of Meetings. Volume 27., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)